Have you ever fancied sailing around the world in your own yacht or buying a holiday home in the Caribbean?
你是否曾经幻想过驾驶着自己的游艇环游世界，或者在加勒比海地区购买一处度假屋呢？
Well, before you get too excited, it may help to find out if you have what it takes to become a billionaire.
嗯，在你过于兴奋之前，先搞清楚一下自己是否具备成为亿万富翁的条件可能会有所帮助。
We've all heard stories of school drop-outs who have made their fortune, but are they the norm or an exception to the rule?
我们都听过一些辍学者发家致富的故事，但他们是常态还是例外情况呢？
Do they tend to be university graduates or self-made entrepreneurs?
他们更倾向于是大学毕业生还是白手起家的企业家呢？
Are they married or single?
他们是已婚还是单身呢？
Thanks to a recent analysis of people in Forbes Top 100 Billionaires List, we can now find out what the world's mega rich have in common.
多亏了最近对《福布斯》全球富豪百强榜上的人进行的一项分析，我们现在可以了解到世界上的超级富豪们有哪些共同之处。
We know which star sign is the most popular amongst multi-millionaires, what percentage wear glasses and even how many are bald!
我们知道在千万富翁中哪个星座最普遍，戴眼镜的人占多大比例，甚至还知道有多少人是秃头！
If you are deciding whether or not to go to university, it may help you to know that 76% of the richest people in the world have a degree.
如果你正在决定是否要上大学，了解到世界上76%的最富有的人都拥有一个学位可能会对你有所帮助。
According to this study, of those 76%, 47% have a bachelor's degree, 23% have a master's and 6% have a doctorate.
根据这项研究，在这76%的人中，47%拥有学士学位，23%拥有硕士学位，6%拥有博士学位。
Don't lose hope if you aren't very academic though.
不过，如果你不太擅长学术方面也不要失去希望。
It's worth noting that many of those on the list did not pass all their exams with flying colours.
值得注意的是，榜单上的许多人并没有以优异的成绩通过所有考试。
Microsoft founder Bill Gates dropped out of Harvard University after two years of study.
微软创始人比尔·盖茨在哈佛大学学习两年后就辍学了。
And Chinese business magnate Jack Ma, failed his university entrance exams three times before going on to complete his degree and make his millions.
而中国商业巨头马云，在完成学位并赚取数百万财富之前，曾三次高考落榜。
Another interesting trend is that the world's high-fliers are much more likely to be married - only 12% of billionaires are unmarried.
另一个有趣的趋势是，世界上的成功人士更有可能是已婚人士——只有12%的亿万富翁是未婚的。
You are also more likely to make it if you were born under the most popular star sign, Aquarius, than if you are a Cancer - the least popular sign on the zodiac.
而且，如果你出生在最受欢迎的星座水瓶座，你成功的可能性要比出生在巨蟹座的人更大。
Finally, the percentage of billionaires who are bald is quite high - so don't worry if you're losing your hair, you may get to sail that yacht around the Caribbean after all!
最后，亿万富翁中秃头的比例相当高——所以如果你正在掉头发，也不要担心，你毕竟有可能驾驶着游艇在加勒比海地区航行的！